featuredrentals.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy / Apartment Hunters, California

_Effective Date: 3/24/2011_

This privacy policy applies to www.ApartmentHunterZ.com owned and operated by Apartment Hunters («ApartmentHunterZ.com»). This privacy policy describes how ApartmentHunterZ.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: www.ApartmentHunterZ.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

ApartmentHunterZ.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the ApartmentHunterZ.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

ApartmentHunterZ.com has been awarded **TRUSTe** 's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by **TRUSTe** for compliance with [**TRUSTe's** program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.ApartmentHunterZ.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us here. If you are not satisfied with our response you can [contact TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). 

This policy will let you know:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you
  2. What cookies are and how they are used
  3. How your information is used
  4. Who is collecting your information
  5. With whom your information may be shared
  6. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
  7. How you can access, update or delete your information
  8. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
  9. Tell a Friend
  10. Links to 3rd Party Sites
  11. Social Media Widgets
  12. How ApartmentHunterZ.com protects children's privacy
  13. Changes to this privacy policy

## What personally identifiable information is collected from you

The ApartmentHunterZ.com collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site.

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, we ask for your name and email address. The system will also ask for your street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, telephone number, and the URL of your web site, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required. This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms (such as the Vacancy posting form) with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to ApartmentHunterZ.com – you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of the ApartmentHunterZ.com.

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place vacancies or take advantage of the other features of the ApartmentHunterZ.com. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Every page within the ApartmentHunterZ.com includes a link to this Privacy Policy.

## What cookies are and how they are used

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, the ApartmentHunterZ.com may use [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Several features of the ApartmentHunterZ.com require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. (See «What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information" for more information on cookies.) 

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes:

  1. To identify and label all «new» vacancies since your last visit to the site.
  2. Optionally to permanently save your password on your computer so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.
  3. To enable you to «checklist and compare» vacancies that you want to mark for future retrieval and viewing.

Third party advertising networks that serve vacancies onto the ApartmentHunterZ.com may also use their own cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. 

The ApartmentHunterZ.com may also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers to let us know what features are effective. 

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

## How your information is used

ApartmentHunterZ.com website is an information resource for individuals looking for rental properties. A user can navigate limited portions of our Site without disclosing any personal information. To get the full benefit of our services we require users to create an account. When you select to sign up for an account, we request your name, phone number, address and credit card information in order to find you the best apartments in your area.

We also use your email to send you rental search results when you express your choice to receive them. We do not share your email address with third parties.

ApartmentHunterZ.com may also collect certain information from visitors to, and customers of the Site such as Internet addresses. This Web Site Navigational Information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, to analyze trends, to track users' movements around the Site, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Site, and our Service. We may also track and analyze individual usage and volume statistical information («Aggregated Information») from our visitors and customers.

## Who is collecting your information

When you are asked for personal information on the ApartmentHunterZ.com, you are sharing that information with the ApartmentHunterZ.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the ApartmentHunterZ.com. For example, when you enter personal information on the Vacancy posting form, this information will generally be included in your Vacancy, unless specifically stated otherwise. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

To request removal of your personal information from a public forum, contact us here. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## With whom your information may be shared

As a general rule, ApartmentHunterZ.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.

ApartmentHunterZ.com may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the ApartmentHunterZ.com or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, other users of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. ApartmentHunterZ.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. If ApartmentHunterZ.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

## What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services of the ApartmentHunterZ.com that require registration in order to participate. These services include the identification of new vacancies that have been posted since your last visit, auto-fillin of the logon form, and the Comparison Shopper feature. You can still use most of the features of the ApartmentHunterZ.com even if you do not accept cookies.

The ApartmentHunterZ.com does not sell, rent or trade user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.

## How you can access, update or delete your information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may edit or delete your user profile at any time by clicking on the «My Profile» link or graphic provided by the system once you are logged in. Once you have logged onto the system during a given session, wherever you go on the ApartmentHunterZ.com, your information will stay with you until or unless you click on the «Sign Out» link, which is accessible from within the «My Profile» screen.

If you are a previously registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may obtain it by email by using our «Forgot Password» feature. Click the button on any login page to request that your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means.

Your ApartmentHunterZ.com account can be deleted, but doing so will result in not being able to access any of the features of the program that require user registration.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information

Other than the administrator of the ApartmentHunterZ.com or other authorized personnel of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. ApartmentHunterZ.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in the ApartmentHunterZ.com. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.

When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, ApartmentHunterZ.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

## Tell a Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. ApartmentHunterZ.com stores [or does not store] this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email [and tracking the success of our referral program]. 

Your friend may contact us here to request that we remove this information from our database. 

## Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of ApartmentHunterZ.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## How ApartmentHunterZ.com protects children's privacy

ApartmentHunterZ.com is a general audience web site. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. ApartmentHunterZ.com does not knowingly collect information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we find that we have mistakenly collected information from a child we will take the necessary steps to delete the information immediately. If you feel that we have collected information from a user under the age of 13 please contact us and we will delete it.

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Us

Apartment Hunters Inc.

32565 Golden Lantern St, Dana Point, CA 92629 USA

Phone: +1 310-982-2536

Email: support@apartmenthunterz.com
